Love, Fall & Order is a tv movie, romance film directed by Clare Niederpruem.
When Claire goes home to save her dad's annual Fall Fest on her family's pumpkin farm,
sparks fly with an old rival – the opposing lawyer she now faces in court.
Claire Hart, played by Erin Cahill.
Hank Hart, played by Gregory Harrison.
Patrick Harris, played by Trevor Donovan.
Aunt Margie Wright, played by Jan Broberg Felt.
Betsy, played by Hailey Smith.
Nick, played by K.C. Clyde.
Breeda Wool is an American actress, writer and producer.
She is best known for her roles as Lou Linklatter in
the Audience crime drama series Mr.
Mercedes (2017–2019) and Faith Duluth in the
Lifetime/Hulu drama series UnREAL (2015–2018).
Her major film credits include AWOL (2016), XX (2017), Automatic at Sea
(2016), Erasing Eden (2016) and Craters of the Moon (2013).
Wool also appeared as Victoria in the Amazon digital series Betas (2013).
She made guest appearances in Freeform's Famous in Love (2017–2018), NBC's Midnight, Texas (2017–2018), Law & Order: Special Victims Unit, two episodes of
Law & Order: Criminal Intent (2001–2011), the two-hour series finale of CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000–2015), and HBO's Room 104 (2020).
The film explores themes of farm, high school, utah, lawyer, injured leg.
The tone is emotional.